We...knowsley...okay.
We're ready to start alright gas.
...we know we have a lot of dedicated people...six thirty.
We're happy to have everybody here and we know
everybody here loves the web and they love the web more than standing in line for the...
Or they want to...sit down while they wait...right so I'm the
...I'm kevin hill lead program manager for the web and frameworks team that microsoft chris
andersen...dev I worked on the...js framework and, work in a variety of things nowadays
to radio I love this stuff.
We...you guys looks like you get prizes if you scan these...
is really cool don't worry this is on the last slide...you play...
What we talk about today is really best...is kind of a journey
of frameworks microsoft and how many people have used wind yes?
...all right
...a good number and,...how many of you guys remember we open-source
when js last year at the last build a few fewer hands.
But, what I do a semester just with a little bit of information about web apps
...microsoft and just kind of give a quick history and,
then we're actually in a quickly move into demos because last thing I think you guys really want to see the...conferences
...although twitter does tell me different during keynote so, we're going to talk about a responsive apple made
is called charm apple tell you what char map is if you don't know don't worry?
And, then we're actually going to take this app
and then rebuild it in another framework in knockout,
knockout js developers...a few those words...alright
...out yes then we're going to do some crazy we'll reveal the of an angular and add another feature.
In...when you guys right here.
And, they're going to go and rebuild the up again and react js and had another feature.
...top off the evening we're going to show you are bootstrap theme that is also
open-source
and it's great for websites that the journey we're going on I love that journey I'm
...journey with you will you join me well you all join us.
All right so I just wanted to talk a little bit about
...microsoft if you look at this timeline you know,
I graduated high school around the time active-x came to be right so it's been a
little while but you go way back then and we were already trying to find ways to extend the web
and in active-x was out there without active-x was great
...hey what do we make height html applications
...who remembers html css html applications a few hands who's made one,
yeah, they were my go-to in college who still having to support one that
you accidently deployed your enterprise...right and then,
you know,...is actually there's even another step we made web components I mean there
is a https which was kind of a web component implementation of
https.
...we started getting into the browser...if you
...a lot of them but you'll see we had a seven ninety eight.
We had office...that showed up inine and
And, then we talked about universal api is
...javascript and...web apps...this conference you guys see the keno demos
flight arcade twenty-two tracks great there's actually session
down earlier today on hosted web apps...you didn't get to go to it you can check it out online later.
You know, you...there's a bit of...gap in that timeline, you know,
we've done a lot on the web microsoft those dots obviously don't represent everything we've done for web
...but it's kind of the app centric investments we're making.
You know, I went and I did a search on some frameworks
...kind of give people idea of timeline of one some of these javascript...to...you know,
script calculus ...alicia is superb delicious tribulations
...was so hot, yeah, I actually...use it but
...came and twenty-six anybody is script delicious one hand
...right who tools.
...here...have a knockout...sss good and then you know,
anglers release actually quite recently but it was actually release
a little bit before I thought it was and then ...of react right
there's, there's like over twenty thousand stars on the get of reactor thing the thing
is popular does that mean you can see like this data showing like how many people are kind of
interested in using it, you know, it's quite interesting because there's so many javascript frameworks I
...even...all on a slide I could even come close to...all the
dates I tried but, the interesting one is actually if you look at how these compared
aj query decrees kind of go to the library in framework on the
web in its switches down all these other all these are the libraries like they're really representing kind
of a small portion however...important there's a lot of lot of people that will start
...with these frameworks so we've been trying to pay attention to the ones that
are getting traction and we've been making investments to have
...hard html controls work well with these other frameworks?
There's a really important emerging framework this is kind of fun slide.
Who's heard of elevator js.
It's got three thousand stars and get have.
...my animation so I click on
...early observed elevator js is a very important framework
...partly because they have a darling and...
In their comments...this that's a javascript frame acknowledge does is going page
...to the top that's more of a joke but just making a point like there's so many javascript
...out there you'll never be able to keep up with them all.
Thanks chris.
All right so what I'm going to do is I'm going to talk a little bit about the investments we've made
in our where application platform everyone here about microsoft edge.
You browser right so microsoft edge looks a little bit like
this to us there's this edge html that the ll.
And, there's this chapter javascript engine and those are the
two main components of the web platform is what we call it
...team I actually works and work on we focus a lot on the edge html the ll.
This is the exact same engine that's available to you as a web developer
...platform you get the same edge html the ll in the same
...javascript engine inside your out.
Of course we love packets content ever since windows
...out one you've been able to make package javascript apps on windows and you can you
can you can include content to have a great offline experience we talked a little bit
...this conference and I mention of front hosted content
posted web applications we made a lot of investments there what we're really trying to do is make it
easy for you to leverage both of these technologies
together mix and match all hosted some hosted...hosted.
Now we've been doing a lot of listing to
developers because even though we made some of these investments I'd say some of the investments
were probably spot on...some of the investments we might have not.
Done in the right way or they might have been not been is used as they could have been we really
hear from developers they just want their existing code to work.
Right more frameworks to work in the windows
eight and a that one timeframe we actually didn't do the best
...that we kinda...you know,
this we focus a bit too much on the windows way of doing things we really we
...focused on interop heavily back in
eighty eight dot one but that's been a huge focus we've had for the microsoft edge
...the security model we had actually who's who ever hit a warning in
our javascript security...said like you can't changer html.
Or you can't...that attribute.
That was actually my...first went to come in write
a javascript up on windows it was before as on the team during windows eight the first thing I
...what's this why do have to run this function called microsoft
app exec unsafe local function to go and do something...felt like it was natural
...the web so, you know, we heard a lot of developer say like this doesn't seem to work well it
was actually not working well for frameworks angular just didn't work out-of-the-box you actually had to go and
...some things and angular actually...actually make...work and, we weren't really playing with the
web development workflow back then right so we made we made quite a few changes to help
...and, are big focus on edge is really the web works if you've been
running markup we've we fixed over seven thousand interop
issues from a eleven to microsoft
edge right so the code you've already written they might have been even webcat focused is
likely to work now obviously you're getting the new rendering engine I talked about the there's a ton of updates
to chocolate if you haven't seen any of the chopper talks, you know,...
online please they've gone over the at even know-how many advancement make them have a hard time keeping
that's pretty incredible the...support rate blossom this is a visual
...to kind of show you all of the different controls and features we have in when
...overall and...is kind of showing you where we focused
on changes so if you're familiar...just kinda gives you a frame of reference and,
I actually I actually kinda want to get to the demos
I'm taking a little longer than I should so what I'm going to do is...I'm going to introduce the responsive
app...made it sound get have...download this code now if you one hack on it that's fine
sands and for requestscharm map so I'm horrible with all those fancy symbols
...the facebook statuses I've senior
...so...chris said hey I got an idea why don't we help you let's make let's make a charm apt to give you some
these cool icons...a modern version of cowed can be a modern version of all these other things
we just we without char map wasn't getting the lovett needed right so we spend some time to
make responsive applicants is a very simple data source...data model I just put the data
...you guys have frame of reference as chris's going through the demos
to show you how we've done a lot of work to make a are controls work with these other frameworks and do some
data bindings so chris what I'm going to do is...overview awesome?
Enough of that silly thing excellent...start right let's just bring up
the app we're talking about here so these are charm site it's live on charm laptop
...websites dot net or com...net but,
we'll just go and look at this really quickly there's the basic version the app
...a list at the top you can scroll through to see what,
you know, simple you want to pick from you can click on this and you get a little dialogue...the details of it and,
that's...the...the home button you go back to the list of the other versions of the app
...the framework we can already see several things in here showing off some of the new controls that we've added
for js in the last year...which is this new split view which allows you to have
the pop out here and you'll notice that as I...window will change behavior
so actually not unless you want...go to the code bandage sars...we'll go to the right place.
We have a...here which shows which allows you see this...so if I go smaller you see
a bar hides and out overlaps content if I go why'd.
...adaptive and now it's going to pin itself out and not obscure the content so
these are kind of those adaptive controls that you see that we talked about a lot of the...entire event we've added
the both the javascript side as well as amazon if we look at this is kind of the is
fairly straightforward html we have a...the talk.
We go through and we have ...view with...what
view we basically have a...area which is that area to the left and we have the rest of the content
becomes your content area one of the things that we invest a lot in is kind of trying to get the details
right of the controls so you'll notice that here we have a second button which is a split view because it turns out that
this the control that's right here in the...version is different than the
...right here because we had to put the different panel that slides out
as we have to do the work to deal with focus management to deal with the styling and
...you set up the dom the right way
then you can have some very simple css rules to control the width and height of those what you want to look like
when it slides out...and the javascript to handle this is simply
...of setting these two properties of...shown display mode hidden display mode
...things that you'll see is that we really tried to adopt some of the feedback we've got
...committee about they want to control more of the feel and look and when these things happen how
the transitions occur we were little opinionated with some of our initial designs of when js where
reads kind of forced some of the windows eight metaphors so we try to do here is make it a little
more flexible and able to handle more a variety of scenarios?
But, we do see is for things like the content dialogue we've gone and spent the time to try to make sure that
this handles a wide variety of screen resolution so as you shrink you'll notice that at some point get
...it snaps the top of the screen in fact
...get even smaller decides it wants to be full-screen then as you get even smaller
...I can't quite make it smaller than edge sorry it'll go full-screen within the
content and all that happens for free with the content dialogue control I can't cook
anywhere else and ui as we get kind of this nice feel but you can control the content and
the display style of that so content dialogues another one of the new controls ingest perfect.
So, I think we want to do is moving on from kind of ...all right.
Thank you get a good button, yeah.
So, like I said this is really a journey of some of the framework so chris really went over
the...js kind of a couple of the new controls we've added there's a few more out there if you want to check amount but,
what we're going to do in this is a really evil check...and chris's I
made him kind of go encode in three different frameworks in the same demo it's actually kind of hard
but, that we have this released on get habits out there today we just put up last night so if you want
...go download the knockout when js adaptor you can do that is still work-in-progress but it's out
there and please play with it and let us know if you have any feedback someone like chris
...add a feature to croatian of socialize it will do that later let's go back
to demo?
All right so.
One of the things that we heard a lot of feedback from the community was that we spent a lot of time
...when js what people really want is to use the frameworks they know and...get some of the rich controls that we spent this
time on building as we've invested in rebuilding these adapters you bridges for all the different
...frameworks so here you see the same app the same functionality of
it all written this time we replaced a lot of the wire up
a lot of the creation with knockout so, we go look at the code for this.
...look at the default html here...we look at the code what we see is
...we're using data
...from knockout are using a template which uses the data
...syntax ...knockout as well so
replaced both the creation list you as well as all of the temple in going on with the
native knockout constructs so we look at the html or a code behind for this we see that
...creating a view model which has a list you array which is
a knockout observable we go down and as we move the slider.
We see apply bindings happening here and then what we do is...the slider we simply
call this update which we go in and just go to the view model and back on the
properties the view model and the ui updates as we can see that you get all of the flexibility
in the polishing the scrolling of the list view with the virtualization all those other pieces
or able to simply integrate with knockout...great chris I thinkthat's
shown how knockouts integrating with control that you should go ahead and add a feature live
...ave literature live ok so they want to do is there's so many great
symbols out there in char map...a powerful important part of my life I want
to keep track of the list of favorite symbols that I have...unicode large
huge so ...do is all...properties of you model in create another observable...
We have a new data model so that's good go.
And, then we...is update or dialogue to have a second bottom so we can actually favorite
push into the data model right so you...is going to go back to the html and
...some of the other layout features like you're saying we need to have the new button.
Okay, so, what are you are in favor of close and we go back to our thing we should see
...is your favorite shown up and you put that all the web so?
So, now...gotta go and do something when favorite
...let's go do that so first thing to do is add a click handler?
W ...think about...I told you it's a very evil trick to chris because you think about...
time right so, first I have to do is going to go and add a handler so once you put the
favor button the way the dialogue returns out as you call show and there's a value that comes back
...so then and,
we say function we get back and event so inside here we can go in and see what the value
is...do is?
I cheated.
On the wrong cheat.
How are demo failure?
This one pretty straightforward...going to say if the event dot result is equal to primary.
We're just going...go to the...model...to the favors list which is
our data item...say hey if you...that primary button pusher the data model which is great
if we go back we see that is actually is happening I love space and I love nine we have
no we've seen favors right we need we need to go and add the to the split...we need to
...the control is not going to show the favors...
chris's tracking within the data model for so he's going to add the button and, bind it?
And,...do.
Favor clicked...the items favorite.
he's just using some of the sander things available...control so we get the favored icon so you have an
...star when he as saves this lovett...live doesn't do anything.
So, you...out...
In you know, chris's using gulp so when he saves is fucked is files are being watched and his
...getting updated live choose...a little bit I'm just going to
...model array I'm just taking a favorites and...the...so, now if we
favored a couple things what than will go here we say that I reluctantly smiley faces.
...service organ just...knockout app.
...see...getting so, the transitions.
For the elements...fading...they're looking...that's...part of the things you
...controlling you'll see that as we go through the other demos which we subject...
All right and then this is just showing like some of the very small code that you would righted knockout
and some of the bindings...showing and is...is coding demo but,
that's there if you want to...look at online layers has fine?
What we're going to do now is we're going to go in use angular js to add another feature and you can see
this is also and get have and...releases library to download and play with now the
feature going to add here is a ratings control because you don't want to just favorite things you want to also be able
to rate things rate let's go back to the
...sank the angular bindings are the most mature of these bridges that we
have knockouts probably the least mature reacts kind of in the middle so,
the angular one we have a much richer one you may have noticed in the knockout example we had a couple places we're still using the
...js binding style
and wire up here the angular one if we open up the markup for we can see that
the every declaration is able to be done using angular directives...really gone through
...done deep integration to make sure that everyone of our controls
and show up and it feels exactly like a native angular...controls so,
here we can see that split view that we saw earlier using the
...js syntax instead here we can see that we have a split view...can see the...commands...wired up
their energy click we can really see kind-of it looks very natural if you're familiar with ...
We want to is...go and, if we look at the javascript we can see that were setting up a module we're setting up
a scope...very little changes in fact you'll notice that here in the view state change
...simply wiring up the scope data to be a new value and,
when we go to our angular version as we scroll through this we see
that updates and changes are able to obviously leverage all of angular binding
and etc it really is the same...redone...there's no knockout and this is not using
...normal ingest syntax so?
Let's go and add the rating control we want to
...that's right that's the first lose will avatar templates we see here are template.
In fact if we just go and scope...this guy here...this guy here.
Greatwe want...do is...ratings so we'll say within the...ratings.
...we see the rating show up we want to set amin value or
...valuations a...value five.
And, the.
User value user rating.
Is ...data bound?
Just space my data mining syntax.
You broke me.
...thank you is going to...to item that data dot
...and that's pretty cool because because you can just go
get the javascript object we can add a rating properties of these controls without making any other changes so,
we save you see now I can star these the
...value if I slide between two sections I come back and
...data still memory that should...updated but it didn't so we'll just ignore that pretend
...save that data although later I'm feeling that's going to bite me and, not work somehow?
All right let's keep going will pretend...will just walk...
Great so we have a ratings were able to update or ui
...actually want to do is add to our scope change the ability to display this they see
...to hear a little bit which I have the favorite button and I'm setting a mode property
on my view state so they can change which data I want to display in the wives going to reuse the same
...list...I want to just...this out so this time we'll do is
...here will say and, you change so now I have my new thing which basically
if the humor's list I do what we did before which is just set the data equal to that character
block array that we saw and otherwise we just go through we grab all the blocks...anybody who has a
rating we do all the all the...the...and if the rating exists we filter...show
the...give me list of the favorites that I know and lob so go here will star couple things.
We'll see if I have to build arithmetic background maybe we don't have a builder and background.
We'll try refreshing...see if that makes everything happier.
...there we go you just...watching the file...but,
yeah, and, one of things you'll see here is that as I star these because we're adjusting the data model the
data the same you'll notice that the top the items that were still net-list actually animated into their new
positions so even though we're using angular we still get all the animations are built into the control that's right.
Possum right so.
It was just showing angular...again I've kind of
...some of the javascript that chris's writing to add this too is you know,
angular scope and then also some of the syntax is that we're using live in
...chris's mentioned under the hood if we go take a look at kind...the
rapping in the directives you can just see that...wrapping the when jess controls in the directive and exposing...so you get
the nice...syntax if you written negative before you're going...really like using these but
...the approach we took on angle one's pretty interesting because the way angular works
under the covers actually worked pretty well with the way that when js worked out-of-the-box
constructors that we used were very easy to expose to directives so the project actually
is a just a little basically list of declarative statements that are the set of properties that we want to
exports into the angular directive system it was a pretty,
pretty straightforward get plugged right all right you ready for one more frame
a feature deep cleansing breath...following along so far I
...I think chris's a doing a great job I want to give
...is easy mineral trippy here now or what but?
So, finally we've just...the react to...as well
as you can go get that on get have just like any of the other...you joined tonight so
...is going to go in add are search feature in react.
So, react I notice that when we asked not everybody in the audience has seen react before so let
me give you a quick overview of kind of the way react works so,
the first thing we can do is if we look at the react
markup the html will notice that react takes a significantly
different stance on markup than what we saw in angular
...angular really lean into the html and did a
ton of new tags and really optimized around having that markup first experience is very declared of
experience in the html angular every angular app that I have seen looks
exactly like this they could all have exactly the same index dot html of
the caching technique or radu but it certainly it makes it easier it's really,
really...on the html and you end up writing a lot of javascript and the big, you know,
the react guys kinda talk about the this new language feature they did of
js x they say well we've been doing this forever with php we've had this extension to
phd ux html literals forever...the very surprised when people get excited about js
acts but what they've done is they've created this ability to
use angle brackets syntax inside of your javascript so, when you see angular
...react markup what you did is a lot of this kind of mix and match
of javascript so here the bottom if the beginning statement which is react dot
render angle bracket app and when you see
...angle bracket in js x what that really means is call it constructor
call with the constructor new function of something called act and
that's exactly equivalent to the code is identical to saying?
New apps paren so the angle brackets are only there to
allow you to reasonably nest
and reasonably use attribute syntax and have child components so,
you get kind of this interesting mix and match of the declared of code?
The other thing that you need to understand about reactors that
reactors of functional programming model which is to say immutable data structures
one-way data transformation and state changes that happen in a separate protocol what that
means pragmatically it you'll notice the top of screen we have this function called
render anytime anything changes in your react app
they-re render one hundred-percent of the content from your apps perspective you create
an entirely new view of the world and they use a technique that actually diffs
the objects that you created on this frame and the object creator next frame to figure out what the
deltas are and they use...approach with the virtual dom that allows them to
do incremental changes to the html dom to avoid a lot of excess overhead
...manipulated...the effect that you get out of this is that with that
straightforward markup you get the ui that you kind of expect to see and as you make changes
dynamically updates the dom with the minimal change the minimal updates
...show how that works and how that plugs into the how
...can participate I can use these controls we wanted to show was adding a new
feature to this react app which kinda shows off the our of react and I can leverage the controls
...a search feature...there's a lot of controls a lot of tags in
...of characters and, what we want to do is an ability to type
in search for one of characters?
...by adding a search button so here and say that we want to have a search clicked.
And, for some reason...called find so, we save.
We'll see we now have a little michael find thing that doesn't do anything.
Great...we want to add a little bit of a state change.
Is all do and, what did you cover the js
x that like the one of the differences when you're when you're writing react code the
...writing using actual ...xfiles this is this actually needs to be
translated javascript so it's very nice syntax...he gets a...
the drop as html there and every time he saves the file watchers going to go and run one of our
...tasks that does the action of transforming the js x
and the javascript this actually run in the web page and, they also have another library
can use that will transform it runtime versus build time which is which is funny use a
...transformer that you can include but,
the syntax is kind of an easy thing to get used to because you can see obviously this
...just break, you know, leaving html in the middle of it without being in a string doesn't seem
like good idea but now you'll see that
...format so it makes it really easy to code and,
functionality feature...js xfiles and I mean even though you're in a js by your
so writing html yet...main html pages pretty clean but you end up making up for by putting it in
your what you can see is what I've done is I had a state property similar to the angular
example where I cheated had this mode for what I want to see on the view what I've done the same thing here I
...state mode for search and list of...the...searcher...default and
you see the react...split view which has a...component of one side of
this of content component of the other as I've toggle them saying when I'm in search
mode the content is going to be something different now is going to be this search...experience and, because of
the way they differ though one of recreating all the controls that they will recreate the ui
...do here is ...do a...search method what this is going to go through and
...grab all the blocks all the characters...available all the things we can...universe we're going
to go and create each for each one of them that matches
...characters...going to walk all of the blocks match
...characters find all the ones that have at least one match and then we have this thing which is only
...the match
we do a javascript map function which actually can take as an array and then it just applies
a functions every element...the...to create a new item in this case we're going to create is a new
...section for each block and then within that will have addictive and
...say now go against every character and...another map function and return
addictive with the item that has a name we want to display?
And, we get to use the awesomely named if you
thought exec unsafe inner function was awesome the react
...upped up with dangerously set inner html.
Which just...love it I am we gotta make sure people know that the content cray
...dangerously right now it is fabulous he's doing a lot of...sayings so,
we've got this up and running and we creative where
...see here we're actually constructing the input text
box so like the weird thing the thing that kind of just blows your mind is hard to wrap your head
...in this model every time you type of character
where we rendering all of this display were rerun during the text boxer re rendering the list
boxer rerun during the split view but all of that gets
ignored because it happens to be the same as a...last time so,
when we go and look at this?
We click...search and we see we get all of our list of items down here and if I start typing.
We see that
...demand...deleting the items that are no longer in there because the
...what we had before what we have now and notice that
...are gone and again even...doing yet another completely different approach to the
why we still are getting the animations the styling.
The behavior of all these controls this using one of our new controls that came to
us when we build the did the phone feature...which is the hub control?
Fabulous let's go back to swords right slides so where we
are journey we've gone through adding three different features and three
...frameworks as
...that side of...some people are taking pictures of the foreign case want to get the url but,
then we'll go ahead and just take a quick...note chris was really doing a good job of explain
because...a spend almost of time on this slide one of the things that you've been seeing
all evening actually is the website that
...been clicking through to go to each one of these apps is actually style with
the bootstrap them well we released a bootstrap theme
that mirrors the look and feel of microsoft websites and that's also up on
our get have account so what we do is show you that theme now and then if you want to
go check it out and have a similar app towebsite look and feel down at the
yes so this case we just have a very simple landing home page and we've
added a little drop down here the lets us toggle between two different...right so,
here you see now we get the kind of the windows style we get the citgo
font which we also have...open-source version that font that's actually available on the get
...but we can obviously toggle between those two using bootstrap exist today so,
what we're trying to do is refactoring js out and find the nuggets
of value that are there like the theme like the styling ...pulls out into the
frameworks that people use today so you can leverage them wherever you are with whatever framework you want to write
...a...to use if you don't want to make the decisions
there is for-you actually go back...sledge real quick?
So, ...I actually lucked out we were able to go to a phone...up
...and how many people here been playing around with...on windows ten?
Get one to awesome well there's another one all
the way over there we just talked about it today and that's actually pretty good so,
I thought, you know, chris's doing all these demos with all these frameworks in that you should probably go make a
cordova app because the early closure
...what's one thing that was one of the html code its the portability yes and,
it would be great if you can you copy all that code and make a cordova apply you
couldn't possibly do that I think we might want to try that okay I think we should awesome so here we go
it will go into this last little bit here so, here I'm in my group the main...use a mega bring up
...and we need to create a new app which we'll call it char map
night senses nighttime...evening and, I need to give it a.
Names...clarice another name.
And, you just I like the name so much I want to...timely manner good so create this course was going
...all scaffolding project will go into this and we need to...we need to add a.
...platform...new platform you...grover.
windows and now the secret address http.
Colon slash a that...slash.
Cordova dash...
All...we went to the wrong thing you'll
...noise went to the others.
...completely unrelated demo that I may not have done earlier today human proxy
...all live...spotty we go through it's going to go sucked down a new definition of the
platform from the site go plug it in and...project we do one other thing which
...tell...configure to add the platform to it so...the configuring
...xml and here many use a new visual studio code.
Because he has...multiple editors do multiple frameworks yet...gotta be
it's gotta be everything ...lot of preference name equals.
Windows dash.
Platform dash version clearly.
Valuable one-zero nintendo okay we don't want to go back and we want
to keep going forward okay and, then we'll do because I love the phone also what a phone.
All right say that...business...to go and there's one other thing if I...we want
to take all that content we've been playing with...we have...just during on or inject writing
...copy and paste and I love robots or new robot copy.
From charm app build into or...
...engine copy that n and cordova.
Run windows...did let's
see I believe we have to worry about the warnings those...some point.
They like...they tell you that something...
Sauna slay.
I might
ask you to do-too-much you moi.
Hill...the.
I feel like that's an error that is because we typed this...this...this line
...because it's not with target...note yes, I should
cut that was my fault chris I blame you entirely so that's good the should work a
little bit of magic
...warnings I feel a little a little edgy when I was going to...are silicate yeah.
...so, here we see that same app running as a cordova app a
...though you build this from the command-line so what would you do to debugged
why would clearly install dev tool that I don't really should I think I think there's
an easier way okay I think you should have twelve that can't work let's try it.
So, even in a cordova app were able to bring up all of the...twelve dev tools your used to using as we
go in...something...hey I love this...I want to change them styles will make
its background...black...make...be read hey look at that.
They're not and that's pretty cool I...
...more I tried to avoid that I know but you...more so chris
did that and he's good at the...coding I'm not-so-good at the live coding so.
You get the goin' going through it so I went ahead and
...amac and I made the same charm
map up and iphone because...of is a great plat cross-platform
kiwi honest cisco check see that I still have the app working obviously
...probably want to do a little bit re-write differently...ui and...code the chris's showing is code...to
...my phone...but the apps...working all right well thank you guys this
is the demos want to show today if anyone has questions we've got...and roomy or
all...you've got...what are you...
...I mean the main point we're trying to make is look we're trying to play well
with a lot of other javascript frameworks and we want to html controls to work for you guys and we love to hear feedback and what
you've seen here if you go and play with the progress and get hub
...request tells what we've done wrong tells we could have done better we love to hear and listen you know,
as you saw...a lot of the talks a microsoft edge is powering all of these
web apps you've seen today on the microsoft platforms and we're always listening logging in eager to talk
so please engage and we'd love to hear more thanks guys...
Any questions please...up-to-the-minute and
then I this is the code the scan if you guys are doing the prizes I didn't want to miss out on that.